guess what if you get a if you learn
Tech and how to code you might be able
to pay for your way through college yeah
yeah because guess what you already know
how to TA you already know how to code
or something like that so even if you're
going to go to college on something is
technology related your chances of
getting a great ta job doing coding a
lot better and then you end up paying
while you're in school and you don't
come out there with a lot of debt so
consider that consider that consider
learning you know some minimal coding or
at least how to you know run a computer
and build them because you might be in
the computers tech support department of
the school and you can sit there and do
your homework for six
hours like I
did and get paid for it there's a lot of
reasons even before College to learn the
skills uh whether it be Tex support Ops
apps coding whatever those are some of
the other reasons